Doramon part 3
this is so wonderful
I wish it can come true
this dream, that dream
all kinds of dreams
all of them can come true
incredible pocket
makes your dreams come true
I want to fly in the sky
no problem
bamboo dragonfly
ononon, my favorite
doramon
why do you care about whose stuff is whose
make sure you will come, I will be waiting
ok, see you
nobita, you just asked sitzuka
for a date, what is it about
I am going to study with her
how can it happen
nobita just asked our sitzuka
unforgivable
situzka
come to my house, ok, let's go
sitzuka went to gian's
I have been looking forward to it
but you are the one who asked her first
why is that
because he forced her
that's why she went with him
now I am not in the mood to study
look
what's that
it says it can make your wish come true
whatever?
Yes, whatever
let me see then I know
for example
dad is bringing some dumplings
back from the bakery right now
it's impossible, because
he is in the office right now
ifs a present
great, ifs dumplings
I went to do some
business visits and met an old friend
he owns a bakery, so he gave me this
I am leaving
can I borrow this
situzka come to my house to study with me
that's it
nobita, your phone
hey, sitzuka
I have made an appointment with you
I will be right there in a bit
I will be here
sitzuka said she will be here in a bit
great
you can make your wish come true by this
Yes
what will happen to this
can't joke on it
doramon and mom dance
and shout on the table
what, I don't do that weird thing
but I have written it on the notebook
damn, treat me like a dumb
I didn't mean to write it down
mom's screaming
what's going on, mom
mouse
I was shocked, really
ok, let's use this to catch giant
situzka is slow
am I right, giant
ok, let's do it
giant and foo make a trick on teacher here
there is sand coming into my eyes use the
glass over there to reflect it and see
what's that face, you see me as a fool
teacher, no, ifs not like that
what a great notebook
only once, I want to talk to shung
sure
situzka and shung have
a conversation at nobita's
are you serious
you will be dead if it doesn't come true
I don't lie
it's true but still
what are you talking about
nothing
nobita, pick up the phone, I am busy now
let me answer it, ok
this is nobita speaking
you are the singer, shung, I am your fan
you are welcome, so bye
he must have made the wrong phone call
but it was like a dream to talk to him
let me have one too
it will be great if it can come true
sitzuka and I kiss here
what did you write
nothing
my heart beats so fast
there is no ink
weird, it was working well
what's wrong
choc
kissing ass lipstick
this is so expensive
it's too fashionable
by the way
what
I have been feeling like something
like what
gold fish
nobita, you are unforgivable
your desert for this week is gone
damn
no matter what
no deserts for me
what's wrong
because I told mom her body
shape is like a gold fish
and then she said she is not going to
give me any deserts
she is easy to get mad
dad, are you painting
I am in the mood to paint today
nobita, what do you think
tell me through your instince
there are delicious apples
bananas, and grapes
I didn't put all the effort on painting
so they look kind of yuchy
give it to me
I am telling you the truth
can't believe you did this to me
I didn't do anything to you
nobita, you are too straight forward
everyone loves to hear nice words
and skips the bad ones
doramon, what should I do
then we have to try this
what's this
kissing ass lipstick
if you put on this lipstick
the other person will be feeling happy
what a retarded dork
doramon, YOU are SO mean
oops, I made a mistake
it's this, kissing ass lipstick
the lipstick earlier is for saying bad
words when you have an argument
let's start it over again
ifs awesome, you look great
really
ifs like this, without knowing
I just kissed your ass
what
let's try
me
like a girl
hurry
(FY
doramon, you are becoming cuter
it's no use to test me
what kind of face is that
how incredible, what the hell
I don't know why mom
didn't go to be a movie star
what are you talking about, nobita
really, you look so beautiful
this cake is for you
I am extremely happy
let me serve you a cup of coffee
made from mom, ifs great
beautiful people always
do beautiful things
stop it, you as a kid shouldn't
be such an ass kisser
dad, I am so lucky to have
you as my father
I just told you not to be an ass kisser
the most respectful person
in the world is dad
I see
I am so lucky
I have such a beautiful mom
and such a wonderful dad
then I got so much pocket money
I felt embarrassed to hear you say that
let's try more
how do you feel today
what's going on, what a weird guy
like a dumb
here is a lipstick
mom
what, you lousy old man
don't break down my house
you sloppy old guy
this is my first time being accomplished
ifs rare, nobita
say something nice
I have got all
it's great this ass kissing lipstick
he is the weirdest person in town
good afternoon, grandpa
you look so healthy and strong
and your beard looks cool too
just like a knight before
if you were to live in old times
you would be a great solider
you are such a nice boy
take these oranges back
thanks
it seems to bite people
look at the teeth, how nice they are
it should be the first dog in japan
thanks, but no, thank you
how can he run so fast
if he is in Olympic game
he will get the gold medal
this is what I stole, if you don't mind
let's stop it right here
ok
lam home
the louiest man in the world
fat like a pig
fat Pig
shit, mom put on the lipstick
that makes you say bad words
asia_cartoons@sinaman.com
missing Grandmom(original)
are you packing
yes, there are too many stuff here
, they need to be cleaned up
don't do nothing there, come help out
unless this bear is
I really miss the old times when I was
little I liked this bear the most
but it's so broken
Grandmom made it for me
you had a grandmom
my grandmom past away
when I was at the kindergarten
yes, there are too many stuff here
they need to be cleaned up
I have some pictures
this one
she looked nice and kind
I still remember what she looks like
grandmom
did someone knock you down again
ok, don't cry
grandmom doesn't like crying nobita
so don't cry
it was the same to your father when
he was little and he always cried home
grandmom
you baby
are you cold
you will catch a cold
put on your warm clothes
why did you break down the glass
your dad will be pissed off at you
as long as he is not injured
help, grandmom
lam not going to forgive you
if you see our nobita as a pushover
thanks, grandmom
I still remember well
about the healthy and strong grandmom
so you liked to cry a lot
when you were a kid
I mean my grandmom was very nice
to me when I was little
please don't get me wrong
sorry
I really want to see grandmom again
ifs too difficult
but doramon, nothing
can really beat you up, right
yes, let's go back there by time machine
again
take me there now
we'd better not to do that
why not
because think about
what your grandmom will think
when she sees you growing up like this
what will she think
she will be happy and jumping around
you bummer
she will be scared and shocked, how can an
old person like her afford this
shocking
but what if we tell her the whole story
it should be all right then
it's too risky, beside
time machine can't change your age
but I really want to see my grandmom
ok, let's just hide ourselves somewhere
and not let her see us
it will work, but you promise
you won't let her see you
I promise
take me there, please
you always say yes
doramon, don't say that
gee
here we are
I miss my yard
orange tree
they out it off last year tho
maybe we can see grandmom
if we climb up the tree
nono, it's no good if she sees us
right
let's go see grandmom
no hurry
don't peek on people here
let's get in
like a thief
the calendar 8 years ago
grandmom usually stays in this room
she is not here
it's weird
will she be in the living room
HO
maybe she is on the second floor
I can't open it
this sliding door is not working well
push it
who are you
mom is really young
yes, she is
really
but soon, you will have many wrinkles
yes, small ones
what did you say
you broke into my house, who are you
I am nobita
let's go
stop
mom probably can't recognize me
how can she
it's better that she can't
missing Grandmom(sequal)
where is grandmom
I came all the way to see her
but still we have to find her
if we stay too long in here
we wont be able to go back home
I was cute huh, when I was 3 years old
now, you are annoying
what
I am telling the truth
foo and giant are knocking down on me
so they started to see you
as a pushover when you were little
ok, show them something
nobita
ouch
you pushed me last time at school
no, you can't do that
but this is the only chance
I have to pay back
ifs no mercy to do
that to such a little kid
I know I was wrong
grandmom
great, ifs grandmom
it's so nice to see her
grandmom, you are home
lam home
did you get me the fire crackers
sorry
I have asked all the stores on the streets
they only sell them in summer
I hate it, I want to play them now
I will look it up tomorrow
great, I wanna play with fire crackers
I hate grandmom, go away
ok
lam not going to allow you
to be bad to grandmom
what are you doing
mom
there is a long story behind it
what are you trying to do
where are you from
is there anything wrong
with you and my family
as a matter of fact, I am nobita
this is nobita
it's not like this
we came by time machine
time machine
poor you, are you sure you are ok
see, no one is going to believe in you
let's go home
let's go
the man right here just now was so weird
mom, dad
ifs grandmom
grandmom
what's wrong with you
why are you so noisy
was there a weird kid coming here
HO
where is he hiding
call the cop
ifs not necessary
please be careful
ok
can we GOING out now
thanks
grandmom, don't you think I am weird
not at all
I feel like you are like somebody
but not a stranger
grandmom, do you think nobita cute
of course
I always want to stay with him
and take care of him
but ifs impossible
besides, I am so old now
please don't say that
at least, you can be alive until
he goes to the elementary school
watch him wearing school uniform
and like a student
ok
what's wrong
please hang on
here you are
doramon, please go back and get
my school uniform back
school uniform
hurry, ifs her wish
but all of a sudden you asked me
to do this,
wait then
why isn't he coming back yet
where did he go
what's wrong with doramon
you are still here
here I am
thanks
great
doramon, I will treat you lots of
dumplings when we go back
just be patient and
wait for a while, really
grandmom
you are not going to believe this
I am nobita going to the elementary school
I see
I always have the feeling
you believe in me, you are not doubting me
who is going to doubt my nobita
grandmom
it's great to see you
go to the elementary school
I will do anything for grandmom
it will be great if I can see your wife
please wait
sitzuka
please marry with me now, can you
don't be kidding
please, this is the only
request in my life
sitzuka
I really can't help you
I am so tired
the beeper to go to the future
what's that
doramon must have done some weird tools
never mind
it's not a good thing to touch
someone's stuff without permission
don't move
you are always like this
you don't really know what it is
and it turns out to be a messy situation
I am going to use this stuff and
still I have lots of things to do
doramon, please come over and help me out
don't touch my thing when I am not around
you don't trust me at all
then I am going to make a mess now
just pretend nothing happened
what's the sound
UFO
so it's a machine to all UFO
calling UFO
if I want to, I can call it whenever
nobita is bullshitting
I am not, just watch
done
where is UFO
here it comes
a piece of cake
I feel good to call UFO whenever I want
how boring
just press the button
the UFO will show up
lam good
you don't need to land on the ground
this place is too small for you to land
alian
hello, hi, good bye
nobita, look what you did
mr. Alian, please wait
I told you not to touch my machine
but
that machine is called the beeper
to meet the future
the alian who gets
this call will come right over
no matter how fat it is
awesome, let's be friends
it's not that easy
you gotta know that they come
all the way from hundreds light years
they will be pissed off
if you have nothing important for them
it might cause a universal war
universal war
what should I do now, doramon
ifs no use to cry on the spoiled milk
lets just see what they will say
it's called translation, eat it up
I am far from the far away planet
you called me several times
it's you, right
Yes
it costs 2 billions for me to fly here
and you called me
while I was having my meal
so tell me what you want
nothing really important
no, you can't tell me this
you see, he is getting angrier
gotta comfort him and send him back
drink it up
it's good, I want some more
drink as you can
make yourself comfortable
he really likes to drink
but if we can make him
feel good to let him go back
Yes
what kind of seal is this
mom, ifs for keeping
the peace in the universe
what are you talking about
how can we buy this kind of stuff
gotta throw it away
are you ok
cheer up
damn
the space ship from the far away
planet is going to attack the earth
please wait, why is it becoming like this
what's wrong
he seems to be very
excited to see the marbles
I have heard that there is no
marbles on that planet
which makes marbles very valuable there
you can have them
for the friendship between
you planet and the earth
please take them with you
bye, take care
great
great, we have saved the earth
from being attacking
nobita and doramon
what the hell that you kids
are drinking beer
unforgivable
mom, it's not what you see
we saved the earth
and we did something great
my teacher
lam counting on you
you should save some money
help yourself
ok, I will smoke less
then I won't go to the beauty salon often
no,
doramon
what, nobita
let's go play
sure
what do you wanna play, yes
to make nobita be much more saver
are you going to buy me something
we want to hire you a tutor
nobita, you have to spend
less on your pocket money
no, I don't need a tutor, no way
you said that but look at
your grades at school
so at least, we have to hire you a tutor
I will be working very hard from
next semester, you just watch
my grades will turn out good
from next semester
what are you joking about
I can't put up with a tutor
lam going to study hard
so be quiet and leave me alone
it's gonna be great if it's true
it's about time for him to come out
ifs been 10 minutes
he must be falling asleep
I knew it
so still, ifs better to hire you a tutor
wait
what do I do now
you say it
I got it, I have a solution
let's go to 3 years from now
and bring back the junior high me
it's a great idea
the junior high me should be able to
solve my elementary questions
let's move
there is no difference between now
and 3 years from now for you
but the house became older
isn't it nice to rebuild it
where is the junior high me
your grades suck, it really worries me
looks like we have to hire you
a tutur if things are going on like this
I told you I don't want that
what's wrong
I became smaller
you are still an elementary school student
I forgot we are at a 3 years later
gotta find out the 3 year later me
nobita, is he there
HO
where is he
he is not here
he could be play outside
now things are not that easy
let's leave him a letter
and then we can go back
I hope you can help me out
with my homework
please come with me to 3 years ago
nobita
me 3 years later
the elementary me
where have you been
I went to look for you I want you
to help me out with my homework
I came for your homework too
ifs my soul mate since he knows
what I want without letting me tell him
exactly
come help me out with my homework
can't be lazy
do it by yourself, that's why I came here
ifs different like I thought
my grades suck and it's all your fault
it doesn't make any sense
it's the truth
if I studied hard when I was an elementary
student, I wouldn't be like this right now
so I will come to see you every day
you have to study hard
doramon, help me
but you are both yourself
if you study hard now
when you get to junior high school
maybe you can get number 2
that's what you think
so here is the junior high me
lam looking for you
anything I can do for you
of course I am here to ask you
to do me something
lam the senior high nobita
if you are lazy in junior high
it causes my problem in senior high
I will tutor you and make you study hard
but I have to look up
at the elementary school nobita
don't laugh, you study hard
let's go
ok, hurry
it seems like
I am always bad at school work
I have to study hard
don't forget after elementary school
it will be junior high
worry yourself first
before you worry someone else
it's now to change your future
don't become like that
you are so lazy
since they are studying so hard
nobita is nobita, I am I
I am studying hard tho
doramon is really irresponsible
asia_cartoons@sinaman.com
nobita in the mirror
the radio control tank is 5680 yen
the radio send
and receive controller is 6500 yen
an then gloves, pants, watch
gotta save some more money
otherwise I can't afford to buy them
here comes dumplings
desert
right
mom, how much are these dumplings
40 each
I don't want it, give me 40 yen
WY“!
I want to save money to buy things
so give me 40 yen
ifs not enough yet
what's wrong
I want to buy a remote
control tank and mini car
you can't have everything you want
but they all have them
whatever
I just want this dumpling
looks yum
that's for me
I know
dig in
I don't want half of it
anyway, you are always like that
ok, I am not going to eat
what's this
more quantity magic mirror
switch it on
what can it make
anything that the mirror sees
it can make the same one
the mirror is awesome
so I just help myself
ifs no good if I forget to switch it off
yes, let's make lots of money
so you can buy whatever
HO
why not
because it's a mirror the things
turn out to be the opposite way
can't do
yes, it's not necessary
that we have to use money to buy it
I only need 30 minutes
you have to give it back to me
and don't break it down
or you have to pay me back
of course, I will pay for everything
and 10 yen for the borrowing fee
and I will give them back the things
after the mirror makes the copy
great, it's just like I am in my dream
now gloves
I think you should stop for a while
you are annoying
it takes only once to turn them
into my things
remember to turn off the switch
afterwards, don't forget
I want this radio machine
and this remote control tank
it's mine now
look at the way he is happy about
it's really joyful
this is awesome, great
who are you
I am nobita
you came out of the mirror, get back there
you are the one who should stay
in the mirror
lam stuck right here, damn, no
I wanted to walk out of the mirror
and had a look in this world
I am going to enjoy myself and have fun
let me out, damn, let me get out of here
it's fun
doramon
what's up
clean up your stuff if you have time
gee, what do you want again
shut up
there is no space for you here
I am going to have fun alone
you get lost
you are really changed
since you have so many toys
nobita
are you still playing
still playing, I just started playing
you have been saying hang on hang on
since this morning
and you are not studying hard at all
I know, I am going to study now
I want to have one more dumpling
one more
by the way, why don't I use the
mirror to make one more to eat
see how you hold your pencil, get it right
but
help
do I really look that weird
I am nobita
help
so who is up there on the second floor
he is the fake nobita
what the hell is this
it's a mess, now do it all over again
HO
wait, nobita, no
I got saved
you Stop
HO
lam going back
the real world is too much
nobita, I am not going to forgive you
this time see where you can hide
you made a mistake, mom, ifs a mistake
doramon, you shut up
mom, you made a mistake
what mistake
aren't you nobita
you are not allowed to give me an excuse
no dinner for you
you study hard right here
you made a mistake
it was the fake nobita, not me
poor you, but this time no excuse
concrete baking tool
lam home
hurry
what's wrong, why are you in a hurry
I Oil!
That's mean
didn't even ask what plan we have
I was going to sitzuka's house to play
never mind, let's go
what if the thief comes in
what should we do
yes, I have a cool stuff
concrete baking tool
lie on the top
on this paper
I feel so weird
ok, you can get up
exactly the same
have him to keep an eye on the house
this is so ugly
you can adjust the position you like
ifs better now
let's go to sitzuka's house now
what kind of attitude you have
wanna fight
damn, gotta let you know how tough I am
jerk
I am so tired
why is it so hard to get you
ifs like you are floating all the time
ok, I will let you go for now
sitzuka, come water the plants in the yard
ok, mom, I will be right over
I am shocked, it's a copied fake man
you guys
yes, what's up there
what's that
ifs a great day; have some rest
is there a thief
cops
wait
stop
you can copy anything you want
even big stuff
you can't drive it
but it looks exactly the same
try it
I really wanna have a ride
how could it be possible
ifs light, so it's floating
ifs a ride too
Yes
there is a pigeon flying
where is nobita
help, I can't swim
help
I can't swim
someone comes to help me
a copied fake man
keeps an eye on the house
help
somebody helps me
too bad
a fake man
nobita
damn
gotta go back home
hurry
where the hell have you been
you are not home
am I too late
nothing I can do right now
just wait to be punished
nobita
this is the kid
he was by the pond at the park
I saved a kid who was almost drawned
don't whose kid he is
it's so touching
so you were the boy
who caught the thief with me earlier
is he your kid
he is such a nice boy
no, you are too nice
lucky that I am not punished
it's all because of him
that I could catch the thief
there is a person with round face
there is a person with long face
there is a person with square face
there is a person with triangle face
cry and be mad, be moody
you cry and you turn out to be the evil
but cheer up and smile
everybody has a round face